Falling in love is a fulltime job
Beauty & the Briefcase is a romance, comedy, tv
movie film directed by Gil Junger.
A freelance writer looking for romance sells a story to Cosmopolitan magazine about
finding love in the workplace and goes undercover at a Finance Company.
Tom Reinhart, played by Michael McMillian.
Lane Daniels, played by Hilary Duff.
Joanne, played by Amanda Walsh.
Liam, played by Chris Carmack.
Kate White, played by Jaime Pressly.
Alicia, played by Jennifer Coolidge.
Beauty & the Briefcase is a 2010 American romantic comedy television film directed by Gil
Junger, based on the novel Diary of a Working Girl by Daniella Brodsky.
The film stars Hilary Duff as a fashion journalist who works
undercover to write an article on dating businessmen.
It premiered on ABC Family on April 18, 2010.
The film explores themes of journalist, based on novel or book,
undercover, dating, co-workers relationship.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.